The kompeito...
The bottle is filling up.
Kobato's wish has changed.
But the contract cannot be changed.
About going to the place she wants to go.
This is more like a curse!
What is going on?
I have to go where I ought to go.
Goodbye.
Wait.
Kobato.
Dou sureba iin dakke?
Atarimae no kototte itsumo
Muzukashii na
Ureshii toki waratte
Suki na toki ni utaitai dake
Na no ni
Itsuka negai wa kanau to
Demo "itsuka" tte dore kurai?
Machikirenai yo
123! no aizu de ryoute hirogete
Zenshin ni hikari wo atsumete
Doko ni aru no?
Oshiete, watashi ni dekiru koto
Meippai kizu tsuite
Seiippai hashitte
Nan juu kai koronde naite
Sore de mo mada
Akireru kurai
Ashita wo shinjiteru
The Day to Come...
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Mother asked us to tidy up the futon.
Futon?
Why would there be bedding in a vacant room?
Oh my.
Fujimoto brought it down for us!
Fujimoto, is your arm better now?
Oh, yes. It's already been a month, after all.
Oh.
Well thank you.
What's that, Mom?
Oh. I'm planning to advertise that room for rent.
It's been vacant since before Fujimoto moved in.
It will get worn down if nobody lives in it.
Is that right?
Ms. Chitose, I'll go in and air the
room out every once in a while.
So why not leave it vacant for the time being?
Why?
Huh?
Sorry. That was an awkward thing to say.
Fujimoto, long time no see.
Is it true about you skipping seminars?
Yeah.
I thought you were working
at becoming a lawyer.
I also heard you haven't been
taking notes lately. What's up?
Nothing in particular.
You know, this isn't like you.
It's like you've lost the will to study.
I'm okay.
Well, there was that incident where you lost
something very important to you.
It's been three months, hasn't it?
It was a real shame, losing that kindergarten.
Yeah. I'm not so concerned
about that, though.
Just...
Just?
Huh?
Uh, no...
It's nothing.
Thank you very much.
Wow!
I heard that the children had been
concerned about Yomogi Kindergarten.
So we all came to take a look!
Fujimoto, you know what?
I'm thinking about rebuilding
Yomogi Kindergarten.
What?
It's Okiura.
He says that this time he will do
everything he can to support me.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you. You hang in there, too.
Yes?
He's been worried about you.
You seem to lack spirit at school.
Domoto and his big mouth.
When things settle down with the preparations,
why don't we all go out on a picnic again?
Sure, that would be great if we all...
We all?
Yes. A picnic with all of us.
All right! A picnic!
That's right!
Hey, where are we going?
I'm coming too!
Sure. Let's all go together.
Right, Fujimoto?
Y-Yes...
Yeah! We'll all be together!
Fujimoto!
You're mean.
I'm sorry.
Kobato is ready!
What the heck?!
What is going on?!
How could this be?
Why doesn't anyone remember her?
Excuse me!
Good morning.
I'm guessing...
You're not here about the newspaper
delivery today, are you?
Yes, I remember her.
Not one person I've spoken to remembers
her, but you do. Why is that?
Is that what you have come to ask me?
Isn't there something else you want to know?
Please tell me.
When she disappeared, I remember she said,
"I have to go where I ought to go."
What did she mean by that?
If you really want to know the truth,
you must listen to what I'm about to
tell you now without being shocked.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
That person lost her life in an unfortunate
incident that occurred long ago,
outside of Ningenkai.
Her life?
Kobato's wish... Her wish was,
that when she is born again in time,
to be by the side of the one she loved.
And to make her wish come true, she was given
permission to come to this land to take a test.
She was provided with merely a temporary
soul to last her just four seasons.
Then...
Has she already arrived there?
That I don't know for sure.
Over many, many years, I have repeatedly
had sad partings with Shuichiro.
Shuichiro? Is he that doctor?
Yes.
But every time he is reborn...
That's right. Every time he is reborn, we meet
and get to know one another all over again.
Our hearts are drawn together.
Even if we have no memory of our previous life.
Because we share the same soul.
As long as I follow my soul,
time and time again, I'm sure...
Fukita Legal Office
Just to think what would have happened
if the machinery in our factory
remained held on collateral...
I can't thank you enough, Mr. Fukita.
I'm so glad it worked out. Good luck
to you and your business.
Thank you very much.
Uh, Fujimoto?
Yes?
There's no rush but I need you to take
a look at the file on your desk.
I'll be away for a while so I want you to handle it.
Okay.
Apparently its an inheritance case.
Mr. Fukita, who's he?
Oh, I guess you haven't met him, Mr. Yamauchi.
Fujimoto has been with our firm
for about four years now.
He's young, but he knows what he's doing.
Fukita Legal Office, may I help you?
Impressive.
Fujimoto, it's for you.
I should bring my son here
to learn a thing or two.
Fujimoto, it's for you.
I should bring my son here
to learn a thing or two.
From the court clerk, Hattori.
I should bring my son here
to learn a thing or two.
Thank you.
The client passed away last month.
His son and daughter-in-law are deceased,
so he had rewritten his will two years ago
so that the sole beneficiary
would be his grandchild.
The problem is that the family
had been there for generations,
and the real estate boundaries are not clear-cut.
I understand. I'll go over to the property
tomorrow and check it out.
Flowers blossom in the spring
Skies in the summer reach far and wide
Every time I...
You're from the lawyer's office, are you?
Pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
Nice to meet you, too.
Even if we have no memory of our previous life.
No! Don't do this! I beg you!
Fujimoto.
You are very precious to me.
You have been...
And you will continue to be. Forever.
The piano...
Huh?
You play it very well.
Uh... I'm sorry. I went ahead and
played it without permission.
For some reason, I know that
song too. Isn't that strange?
Is that right? It's a song a very special
person sang to me many years ago.
I've been looking for her for a very long time.
Really. I hope you find her.
Thank you.
Well then, can I have you come and
confirm the contents in the house?
Yes, of course.
And that's it.
The rest I'll handle after I get back to
the office before I file the procedures.
Yes. Thank you for your help.
Oh and I meant to return this to you.
To me?
Kompeito?
Would you mind singing me that song
one last time before I go?
Okay.
Flowers blossom in the spring
Skies in the summer reach far and wide
Every time I think of this
Precious thoughts spread across in my heart
In the morning when it rains
On those days when the windows stay closed
My heart shimmers with a light
Light shining brightly above...
Uh... Are you all right?
So this was it.
The place I wanted to go.
The place where the person I
most want to be with resides.
I was hoping that if I could meet you
again, this time I'll stay smiling.
But I can't seem to do that.
Kobato?
I'm home!
How many years must I wait?
You're really late this time.
Fujimoto!
Yorokobi, kanashimi,
In happiness and in sadness,
Subete idaite aruiteiru,
In all I behold and all that I live for,
Watshi no te to
With my hand in your hand
Kimi no te wo,
And your hand in my hand,
Tsuyoku tsunagu mono
Together, we are one and whole
Aki wa mizube ni,
Fall hides in the waterside,
Fuyu kozue ni hisomu
And winter hides on the treetops.
Sekai no oku no
The depths of the Earth
Kagirinai yasashisa
Are filled with endless kindness
Yoru ga kuru tabi
Once night falls,
So this is what it boils down to. That fool.
Yoru ga kuru tabi
Once night falls,
Even though he accomplished his mission,
Yoru ga kuru tabi
Once night falls,
Even though he accomplished his mission,
he remains in Ningenkai saying he needs
to keep an eye on her from the shadows.
Inori wo sasageyou
I offer you my prayers
And we end up having to sit around
wasting time in the baumkuchen shop.
Inori wo sasageyou
I offer you my prayers
And we end up having to sit around
wasting time in the baumkuchen shop.
Ashita kuru hi wo
Let us solemnly greet
You got it.
Ashita kuru hi wo
Let us solemnly greet
They're very good, your baumkuchen cakes.
Ashita kuru hi wo
Let us solemnly greet
Shizuka ni mukaeyou
The day tomorrow brings
Well done.
Shizuka ni mukaeyou
The day tomorrow brings
A perfect one hundred points, for me.
Shizuka ni mukaeyou
The day tomorrow brings
Watashi wo michibiku
The voices are calling to me
Tooi, tooi yobigoe yo
From way over yonder, from far I can hear
Hohoemu you ni,
Voices of laughter,
Utau you ni,
And voices of singing
Hibiku kaze no oto
Echoing voices of the wind
Yorokobi, kanashimi,
In happiness and in sadness,
Subete idaite aruiteiru,
In all I behold and all that I live for,
Watashi no te to
With my hand in your hand
Kimi no te wo
And your hand in my hand,
Tsuyoku tsunagu mono
Together, we are one and whole
The End